A Guide to the Environmental Impact Statements of the Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1976-2004
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Environmental Impact Statements, 1976-2004., Extent: 15 boxes. (Box 1-15)
  - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration
    - Final Amendment 12 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan Incorporating the Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement and Regulatory Impact Review, Volume III, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Final Amendment 5 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan Incorporating the Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement, Volume IV, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Final Amendment 12 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan Incorporating the Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement and Regulatory Impact Review, Volume II, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Final Amendment 12 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan Incorporating the Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement and Regulatory Impact Review, Volume I, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Draft Fishery Management Plan for Atlantic Tunas, Swordfish, and Sharks, Volume I, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Department of Commerce/National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration/National Marine Fisheries Service: Draft Fishery Management Plan for Atlantic Tunas, Swordfish, and Sharks, Volume II, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement, Norfolk & Western Railway Company, Coal Ground Storage Facility, Isle of Wight, Virginia, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Appendix, Appendices 1-9, Final Environmental Impact Statement, Norfolk & Western Railway Company, Coal Ground Storage Facility, Isle of Wight County, Virginia, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Surplus Plutonium Disposition Final Environmental Impact Statement, Volume I, Part A, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Surplus Plutonium Disposition Final Environmental Impact Statement, Volume I, Part B, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Surplus Plutonium Disposition Final Environmental Impact Statement, Volume II, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Surplus Plutonium Disposition Final Environmental Impact Statement, Volume III, Part A, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Surplus Plutonium Disposition Final Environmental Impact Statement, Volume III, Part B, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Surplus Plutonium Disposition Final Environmental Impact Statement, Summary, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Disposition of Surplus Highly Enriched Uranium Disposition, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Summary (2 copies), 1995 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Disposition of Surplus Highly Enriched Uranium, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Disposition of Surplus Highly Enriched Uranium, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Volume I, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Office of Fissile Materials Disposition, U.S. Department of Energy, Disposition of Surplus Highly Enriched Uranium, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Volume II, Comment Analysis and Response, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 1, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Summary, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix A, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix B, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix C, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix D, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix E, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix F, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Department of Energy/Environmental Impact Statements-0218D, Volume 2, Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Nuclear Weapons Proliferation Policy Concerning Foreign research Reactor Spent Nuclear Fuel, Appendix G, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Final, Framework Adjustment 16 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan to Address Fishing for Bait in the Harbor Porpoise Closure Areas, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Fishery Management Plan for the Scup Fishery and Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Amendment 5 to the Fishery Management Plan for the Atlantic Mackerel, Squid, and Butterfish Fisheries, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Amendment 12 to the Atlantic Surfclam and Ocean Quahog Fishery Management Plan, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Amendment 8 to the Atlantic Mackerel, Squid, and Butterfish Fishery Management Plan, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Amendment 12 to the Summer Flounder, Scup, and Black Sea Bass Fishery Management Plan, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Final Amendment 11 to the Northeast Multispecies Fishery Management Plan; Amendment 9 to the Atlantic Sea Scallop Fishery Management Plan; Amendment 1 to the Monkfish Fishery Management Plan; Components of the Proposed Atlantic Herring Fishery Management Plan for Essential Fish Habitat Icorporating the Environmental Assessment, Volume II (Box 14)
    - Initial Consultation Package, Luray/Newport Hydro Stations, FERC Project No. 2425, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Final License Application, Luray/Newport Hydro Stations, FERC Project No. 2425, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Appendices, Final License Application, Luray/Newport Hydro Stations, FERC Project No. 2425, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Attachments, Final License Application, Luray/Newport Hydro Stations, FERC Project No. 2425, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Environmental Report for the Bandy Water Line Extension, 2001 (Box 15)
    - Coalfields Expressway - Final Environmental Impact Statements, 1999 (Box 15)
    - Coalfields Expressway - Draft Environmental Impact Statements, 1999 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Naval Nuclear Propulsion Program, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Occupational Safety, Health, & Occupational Medicine Report, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Occupational Radiation Exposure from Naval Reactors' Department of Energy Facilities, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Occupational Radiation Exposure from U.S. Naval Nuclear Plants & Their Support Facilities, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Environmental Monitoring & Disposal of Radioactive Wastes from U.S. Naval Nuclear-Powered Ships & Their Support Facilities, 2004 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy - Office of Environmental Management - Final Waste Management Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement for Managing Treatment, Storage, & Disposal of Radioactive & Hazardous Waste, Volume I, 1997 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy - Office of Environmental Management - Final Waste Management Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement for Managing Treatment, Storage, & Disposal of Radioactive & Hazardous Waste, Volume II, 1997 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy - Office of Environmental Management - Final Waste Management Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement for Managing Treatment, Storage, & Disposal of Radioactive & Hazardous Waste, Volume III, 1997 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy - Office of Environmental Management - Final Waste Management Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement for Managing Treatment, Storage, & Disposal of Radioactive & Hazardous Waste, Volume IV, 1997 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy - Office of Environmental Management - Final Waste Management Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement for Managing Treatment, Storage, & Disposal of Radioactive & Hazardous Waste, Volume V, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Reverse Index - Guide to Commentators Organized by Comment/Response Number 1997 (Box 15)